Friends, Dreams, and a Rockin' Adventure!
The Barbie Diaries is a family, animation film directed by Kallan Kagan.
Barbie is disheartened when Todd breaks her heart and
goes back to his former girlfriend.
But things change when she comes across a diary,
which makes her wishes come true.
Barbie (voice), played by Kelly Sheridan.
Courtney (voice), played by Sarah Edmondson.
Tia / Passing Girl #2 (voice), played by Venus Terzo.
Kevin (voice), played by Matt Hill.
Raquelle (voice), played by Chiara Zanni.
Regen (voice), played by Maryke Hendrikse.
The Barbie Diaries is a 2006 animated motion capture teen drama film directed by Eric Fogel and
written by Elise Allen and Laura McCreary which premiered on Nickelodeon and then on DVD.
The eighth entry in the Barbie film series, it features Kelly Sheridan as the talking
vocal provider for Barbie and Skye Sweetnam as her singing vocals.
The only Barbie film produced by Curious Pictures and thus the only film in the first decade of the Barbie film franchise not to be produced by Mainframe Entertainment (currently Mainframe Studios), this is also the last Barbie film to be originally distributed by Lionsgate in the United
States and Canada, as Universal Studios (now Universal Pictures), who already released the films overseas with international distributor Entertainment Rights, was set to take over the home video distribution rights from the next film, Barbie in the 12 Dancing Princesses.
The film explores themes of high school,
friendship, diary, rivalry, based on toy.